# **Julio Gerald Premaldy Philippus**

# **Web Developer**

+62 851-7956-3275 || juliogp.philippus@gmail.com || Yogyakarta, Indonesia linkedin.com/in/juliophilippus

#### **About Me**

A recent Bachelor of Information Systems graduate from Duta Wacana Christian University (DWCU) with a specialization in web development. Possessing practical experience in building congregation management systems using Laravel and Bootstrap framework. Driven by a passion for learning new things, I am continuously developing my skills and knowledge in web development. Accustomed to working in teams and possessing strong problem-solving abilities.

#### **Education**

### **Duta Wacana Christian University**

(Aug, 2018 – Jul, 2024)

GPA: 3.54 / 4.00

Bachelor of Information Systems

I was a student majoring in Information Systems with a strong interest in web development. During my studies, I was actively involved in various committees and organizations, which helped me develop leadership skills and teamwork.

#### **Job Experiences**

#### Internship Full Stack Developer, GPIB Maranatha Tanjung Selor

(Jun, 2023 – Jun, 2024)

- Developed a congregation management website and dashboard using Laravel framework.
- Managed a MySQL database to store congregation data.
- Implemented Bootstrap framework for responsive design.
- Implemented JavaScript to add some features.

#### Internship Back End Developer, GBI Ngadinegaran Yogyakarta

(Aug, 2021 - Dec, 2021)

- Developed a congregation management website using Laravel framework.
- Managed a MySQL database to store congregation data.
- Implemented JavaScript to add some features..

# **Project Experiences**

#### Full Stack Developer, YYY Coffee

(Aug, 2024 - Present)

- Developed a sales point application for YYY Coffee using the Laravel framework.
- Managed a MySQL database to store sales transactions and inventory data.
- Implemented the Bootstrap framework for a responsive and user-friendly interface.
- Utilized JavaScript and jQuery to enhance interactivity and dynamic features.

## System Analyst, SiAnji

(Feb, 2021 - Jun, 2021)

- Designed application architecture to meet business requirements and system objectives.
- Prepared complete documentation, including functional specifications, system design, and technical documentation.
- Created detailed and user-friendly manuals to ensure users can effectively operate the system.
- Collaborated with developers and stakeholders to ensure system implementation met business requirements.
- Delivering project presentations and system solutions to clients, as well as providing explanations on system functionality and benefits.

#### **Additional Information**

Hard Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Laravel, Bootstrap, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Problem Solving, Detail Oriented, Responsible

#### Certifications

1.	Fundamental Front-End Web I , Coding Studio	(Aug, 2024)
2.	Fundamental Databae MySQL	(Aug, 2024)

Proficient in Building Websites with Laravel 9, Coding Studio

(Aug, 2024)